Laura Musso

About me

I'm an enthusiastic developer with a keen eye for design. I focus on creating user-friendly digital experiences and enjoy learning new technologies. I excel in collaboration, clear communication, and creative problem-solving while effectively managing my time to meet deadlines. I am adaptable, dedicated, and fluent in English, Italian, Spanish, and Portuguese.

Skills

Soft Skills:

- Strong communication skills, problem-solving and team collaboration.
- Experienced in delivering workshops and creating clear, comprehensive documentation.

Core Frontend Skills:

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- Vue3.js, React, Next.js

Backend & Database Skills:

• SQL Server

Scripting & Automation:

• Bash

Deployment Tools:

· Netlify, Docker

Design Skills:

 Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign

Contact Me



https://github.com/lauramussopd

Work Experience

September 2024 - Present

Consultant Akkodis

- Develop scripts in Bash to automate processes and enhance efficiency.
- Manage and analyze data, primarily working with SQL Server.
- Deliver workshops and presentations, ensuring effective knowledge transfer to clients and stakeholders.
- Document workflows and project outcomes with precision to support team collaboration and future reference.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams, fostering a solution-oriented approach to complex challenges.

2021-2024

Frontend Developer & Technical Support Specialist Etnia Eyewear Culture

- Develop and maintain front-end components with Vue and Typescript for company websites, ensuring a seamless user experience.
- Identify software bugs, open detailed tickets, and follow up to ensure timely resolution.
- Assist the sales team by responding to customer inquiries, processing orders, and maintaining sales databases (SAP / C4C).

Education

January 2024 - May 2024

Ironhack - Front End Web Development

Vue3.js, Composition API, Supabase and SQL

Nov 2022 - December 2023

42 Barcelona - Computer Science

C, Git, Github

2016-2019

Ca' Foscari Venice - Master's degree, Art History and Cultural Heritage